Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/jeff-sullivan-2360a516 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Capital Markets
Investments
Asset Management

Languages

English French

Certifications

CFA
Series 7
Series 79
SIE

Jeff Sullivan

Senior Vice President, Global Relationship Manager at HSBC Boston, Massachusetts

Summary

Knowledgeable, energetic, and self-motivated finance professional. Experienced with developing and maintaining a portfolio of clients, prospecting new clients, geographic business expansion and execution of new business strategies. Deep understanding of credit, corporate finance and capital markets applied to a broad spectrum of industries. CFA Charterholder.

Experience

HSBC

Senior Vice President, Global Relationship Manager August 2018 - Present (2 years)

Greater Boston Area

Northern Trust Corporation Senior Vice President 2017 - 2018 (1 year) Greater Boston Area

Citizens Bank Senior Vice President 2015 - 2016 (1 year) Greater Boston Area

The Northern Trust Company Senior Vice President 2005 - 2014 (9 years) Chicago, IL

JPMorgan Chase Corporate Banking 1997 - 2005 (8 years)

Education

Babson College - Franklin W. Olin Graduate School of Business MBA, Finance

College of the Holy Cross Bachelor of Arts - BA

Deerfield Academy